The Amanda Seale Show, today's bingo bingo, goes to the Alaska Airlines door that flew off,
leading to the Boeing CEO's resignation. Yeah. Boeing CEO Dave Calhoun will step down at the
end of the year, along with other key executives. The door is now in witness protection because we
know how Boeing and them gets when it comes to whistleblowers. So I would like to read an open
letter to the door. Dear door, I just wanted to drop you a quick note to say thank you. You
really took one for the team by flying off and causing all that chaos that eventually led to
the resignation of the Boeing chief executive officer with gratitude. Yo girl, Amanda. Today's
letdown goes to Fins Up Water Park in Lake Lanier, Beaufort, Georgia. There is a water park that is
set to open on Lake Lanier, which is known by the locals to be haunted. Now we got our hands on a
list of the rides that are going to be at this water park. The Phantom Plunge, a water slide where
riders are plunged into the depths of a watery grave for disturbing these people's resting place.
Zombie zipline. Riders soar above the water park on a zipline haunted by the angry souls of the
displaced who reach out from below, watch your foot, to grab your goofy ass down for trespassing on
their land.